(Penny:)Um, yeah. Starting with the champagne
a little early, aren't you?
(Raj:)It was in the limo.
They sent a limo. I have a limo.
I just love saying "limo." Here.
(Raj:)- Sip on this while you're getting ready.
- Oh, I'm ready.
That's what you're wearing?
Um, yeah. Why? What's wrong with it?
(Raj:)Nothing. I was just hoping for something
a little more, you know, ridonkulous.
Yeah. Well, this is all the "donkulous"
you're gonna get tonight.
Okey-dokey. Let's roll.
All right, it's time to raise the roof.
Ooh-ooh.
(Penny(to Leonard who is just coming up the stairs):)Hey, Leonard.
- Hey.
- Dude.
- You look very nice.
BOTH: Thank you.
(Penny:)- Come on. Good night, Leonard.
- Good night.
- Leonard, did you see my limo downstairs?
- Yeah.
(Raj:)It's bigger than the house
my grandfather grew up in.